[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 22, "question": "Just don't play with her with tennis, right?", "question_tokens": ["Just", "do", "n't", "play", "with", "her", "with", "tennis", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "IN", "NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 23, "answer": "I wouldn't have a chance.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "n't", "have", "a", "chance", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 43, "question": "Have you seen the president, by the way?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "seen", "the", "president", ",", "by", "the", "way", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 44, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 45, "question": "You'd (INAUDIBLE)?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'d", "(", "INAUDIBLE", ")", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 46, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 49, "question": "Who was more boy crazy?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "was", "more", "boy", "crazy", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "JJR", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 50, "answer": "This one is always boy crazy.", "answer_tokens": ["This", "one", "is", "always", "boy", "crazy", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "110916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 56, "question": "What more can a man give you?", "question_tokens": ["What", "more", "can", "a", "man", "give", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "JJR", "MD", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 57, "answer": "That's what I'm saying, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "what", "I", "'m", "saying", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 70, "question": "You're on a CNN show, right?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'re", "on", "a", "CNN", "show", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 71, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 74, "question": "What is the serious side of Mario like?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "the", "serious", "side", "of", "Mario", "like", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 75, "answer": "Well, you know, I fancy myself a news guy.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "I", "fancy", "myself", "a", "news", "guy", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mario"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 113, "question": "What were the values?", "question_tokens": ["What", "were", "the", "values", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 114, "answer": "I think it was just a strong work ethic.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "was", "just", "a", "strong", "work", "ethic", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 128, "question": "What do you think attracted them to America?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "attracted", "them", "to", "America", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "PRP", "TO", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 129, "answer": "It's still the land of opportunity.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "still", "the", "land", "of", "opportunity", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 137, "question": "What do they make of what happened to America?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "they", "make", "of", "what", "happened", "to", "America", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "WP", "VBN", "TO", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 138, "answer": "You know, it's funny.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "it", "'s", "funny", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 143, "question": "Can she not even say, Mario, what have you done to your teeth?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "she", "not", "even", "say", ",", "Mario", ",", "what", "have", "you", "done", "to", "your", "teeth", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "VB", ",", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 144, "answer": "Brush them.", "answer_tokens": ["Brush", "them", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mario"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "PRP", "TO", "VB", ",", "RB", ",", "CC", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 156, "question": "What do you think the answer is?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "the", "answer", "is", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 157, "answer": "You know, I think we have no one to blame, really, but ourselves.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "think", "we", "have", "no", "one", "to", "blame", ",", "really", ",", "but", "ourselves", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 171, "question": "Are you a fan of the president?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "a", "fan", "of", "the", "president", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 172, "answer": "OPEZ: I am because I got to spend time with him.", "answer_tokens": ["OPEZ", ":", "I", "am", "because", "I", "got", "to", "spend", "time", "with", "him", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "CC", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 176, "question": "He was on your show?", "question_tokens": ["He", "was", "on", "your", "show", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 177, "answer": "He was on my show, believe it or not.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "was", "on", "my", "show", ",", "believe", "it", "or", "not", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 190, "question": "Is America more or less racist for having had its first African-American, nonwhite president?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "America", "more", "or", "less", "racist", "for", "having", "had", "its", "first", "African-American", ",", "nonwhite", "president", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "NNP", "RBR", "CC", "JJR", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "VBD", "PRP$", "JJ", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 191, "answer": "I think you still have the same issues, to tell you the truth.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "you", "still", "have", "the", "same", "issues", ",", "to", "tell", "you", "the", "truth", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NNS", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 201, "question": "What are your old friends maybe from the old neighborhood when you get back there?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "your", "old", "friends", "maybe", "from", "the", "old", "neighborhood", "when", "you", "get", "back", "there", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 202, "answer": "The same friends I got right now.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "same", "friends", "I", "got", "right", "now", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "RB", "RB", ",", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", ",", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "NNS", ":", "NNS", ",", "NNS", ",", "NNS", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 205, "question": "What are their biggest concerns in reality, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "their", "biggest", "concerns", "in", "reality", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP$", "JJS", "NNS", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 206, "answer": "The reality right now, the barber shop talk, if you will, everyone is concerned about jobs -- jobs, jobs, jobs, jobs.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "reality", "right", "now", ",", "the", "barber", "shop", "talk", ",", "if", "you", "will", ",", "everyone", "is", "concerned", "about", "jobs", "--", "jobs", ",", "jobs", ",", "jobs", ",", "jobs", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 242, "question": "And your show sort of fits, you take celebrities to meet their haters, right?", "question_tokens": ["And", "your", "show", "sort", "of", "fits", ",", "you", "take", "celebrities", "to", "meet", "their", "haters", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 243, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 262, "question": "Have you been particularly hurt by the stuff you read about yourself?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "been", "particularly", "hurt", "by", "the", "stuff", "you", "read", "about", "yourself", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBN", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 263, "answer": "I've been bothered by the way it affects my family.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'ve", "been", "bothered", "by", "the", "way", "it", "affects", "my", "family", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NN", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 264, "question": "What's the worst stuff for you to deal with?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "the", "worst", "stuff", "for", "you", "to", "deal", "with", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 265, "answer": "Oh, nothing too terrible.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "nothing", "too", "terrible", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 312, "question": "As a guilt ridden Catholic boy, you've been this lady, the mother of your child for three years now?", "question_tokens": ["As", "a", "guilt", "ridden", "Catholic", "boy", ",", "you", "'ve", "been", "this", "lady", ",", "the", "mother", "of", "your", "child", "for", "three", "years", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NNP", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 313, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 315, "question": "Are you going to get married?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "going", "to", "get", "married", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 316, "answer": "It's coming.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "coming", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 318, "question": "It is?", "question_tokens": ["It", "is", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 319, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "RB", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "RB", ",", "RB", ",", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 336, "question": "How did you get married for two weeks?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "you", "get", "married", "for", "two", "weeks", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 337, "answer": "I was not mature enough and I didn't have the guts really, probably, to do the right thing.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "was", "not", "mature", "enough", "and", "I", "did", "n't", "have", "the", "guts", "really", ",", "probably", ",", "to", "do", "the", "right", "thing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "JJ", "CC", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 342, "question": "Do you think you've met the one now?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "you", "'ve", "met", "the", "one", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "CD", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 343, "answer": "Those sort of things become redundant and yes, I have.", "answer_tokens": ["Those", "sort", "of", "things", "become", "redundant", "and", "yes", ",", "I", "have", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mario Lopez"]}, "docId": "110916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 349, "question": "Do I have it in me?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "I", "have", "it", "in", "me", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 350, "answer": "Yes, Mario Lopez.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "Mario", "Lopez", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 351, "question": "Mario, do you think you have it in you?", "question_tokens": ["Mario", ",", "do", "you", "think", "you", "have", "it", "in", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 352, "answer": "That's pretty good.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "pretty", "good", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mario"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 353, "question": "Mario the lothario, do you think you have it in you?", "question_tokens": ["Mario", "the", "lothario", ",", "do", "you", "think", "you", "have", "it", "in", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 354, "answer": "Oh, God!", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "God", "!"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 362, "question": "Ten percent?", "question_tokens": ["Ten", "percent", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CD", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 363, "answer": "That's about 4,000 women.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "about", "4,000", "women", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 378, "question": "Is that the kind of job you would love to have?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "the", "kind", "of", "job", "you", "would", "love", "to", "have", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 379, "answer": "I'm honored by those rumors.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "honored", "by", "those", "rumors", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 389, "question": "Are you in discussions for the job?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "in", "discussions", "for", "the", "job", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 390, "answer": "Well, I mean, you know -- I've, like in, I filled in before.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "you", "know", "--", "I", "'ve", ",", "like", "in", ",", "I", "filled", "in", "before", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 397, "question": "Did you see me?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "see", "me", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 398, "answer": "Yes, of course I did.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "of", "course", "I", "did", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 399, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 400, "answer": "Out of the 27 reasons I want to hate you, is because you're a great dancer.", "answer_tokens": ["Out", "of", "the", "27", "reasons", "I", "want", "to", "hate", "you", ",", "is", "because", "you", "'re", "a", "great", "dancer", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ",", "RB", ",", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "CC", "VBP", "TO", "PRP", "CC", "VBD", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "RB", "IN", "TO", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 409, "question": "What do you think as a former contestant and someone in the world of entertainment?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "as", "a", "former", "contestant", "and", "someone", "in", "the", "world", "of", "entertainment", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 410, "answer": "I, too, had the opportunity to interview him and talk to him and found him to be a really nice guy and very down to earth.", "answer_tokens": ["I", ",", "too", ",", "had", "the", "opportunity", "to", "interview", "him", "and", "talk", "to", "him", "and", "found", "him", "to", "be", "a", "really", "nice", "guy", "and", "very", "down", "to", "earth", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "IN", "JJ", ",", "RB", ",", "IN", "JJ", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ",", "DT", "NN", ",", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "``", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "''", ":", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBG", "DT", "DT", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 417, "question": "What would your message be to those people?", "question_tokens": ["What", "would", "your", "message", "be", "to", "those", "people", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 418, "answer": "Well, just in general, again, that hate is not good and you should sort of take the time to sort of get educated on the topic, the person, what he's been through, and you took a giant leap forward to commit to doing something like \"Dancing with the Stars\" -- knowing that he is a smart guy, knowing all that would come with it.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "just", "in", "general", ",", "again", ",", "that", "hate", "is", "not", "good", "and", "you", "should", "sort", "of", "take", "the", "time", "to", "sort", "of", "get", "educated", "on", "the", "topic", ",", "the", "person", ",", "what", "he", "'s", "been", "through", ",", "and", "you", "took", "a", "giant", "leap", "forward", "to", "commit", "to", "doing", "something", "like", "``", "Dancing", "with", "the", "Stars", "''", "--", "knowing", "that", "he", "is", "a", "smart", "guy", ",", "knowing", "all", "that", "would", "come", "with", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 441, "question": "How are you, Piers?", "question_tokens": ["How", "are", "you", ",", "Piers", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 442, "answer": "Good, thank you.", "answer_tokens": ["Good", ",", "thank", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "NN", "MD", "VB", "NN", "CD", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 445, "question": "What will make sense?", "question_tokens": ["What", "will", "make", "sense", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 446, "answer": "Hopefully, life will make sense one day.", "answer_tokens": ["Hopefully", ",", "life", "will", "make", "sense", "one", "day", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 448, "question": "Do you have any confidence of that?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "have", "any", "confidence", "of", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 449, "answer": "I do believe that some things will happen.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "believe", "that", "some", "things", "will", "happen", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 455, "question": "What was your take looking back on it?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "your", "take", "looking", "back", "on", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "VBG", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 456, "answer": "Originally I laughed at it.", "answer_tokens": ["Originally", "I", "laughed", "at", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 463, "question": "Did they not really understand the culture that you were talking about?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "they", "not", "really", "understand", "the", "culture", "that", "you", "were", "talking", "about", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 464, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 485, "question": "What did he say about it all?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "he", "say", "about", "it", "all", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 486, "answer": "I mean, he just thanked me for attending and I thanked him for inviting me.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "he", "just", "thanked", "me", "for", "attending", "and", "I", "thanked", "him", "for", "inviting", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "RB", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 493, "question": "But anyway, what did you make of it?", "question_tokens": ["But", "anyway", ",", "what", "did", "you", "make", "of", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", ",", "WDT", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 494, "answer": "I definitely knew that he would definitely then do -- they didn't do the research on Common.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "definitely", "knew", "that", "he", "would", "definitely", "then", "do", "--", "they", "did", "n't", "do", "the", "research", "on", "Common", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 504, "question": "What's your view on how he's performing?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "your", "view", "on", "how", "he", "'s", "performing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 505, "answer": "I tend to differed with believing that he didn't fulfill the hope.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "tend", "to", "differed", "with", "believing", "that", "he", "did", "n't", "fulfill", "the", "hope", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "JJ", ":", "IN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "IN", "VBG", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VB", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 513, "question": "What is the one thing you think that really needs to be fixed that hasn't been fixed?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "the", "one", "thing", "you", "think", "that", "really", "needs", "to", "be", "fixed", "that", "has", "n't", "been", "fixed", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "CD", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "RB", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 514, "answer": "I believe that if we can instill in them self-love -- because obviously if we give a child some hope through education and through fulfilling their dreams, then they will like keep their eyes on the prize.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "believe", "that", "if", "we", "can", "instill", "in", "them", "self-love", "--", "because", "obviously", "if", "we", "give", "a", "child", "some", "hope", "through", "education", "and", "through", "fulfilling", "their", "dreams", ",", "then", "they", "will", "like", "keep", "their", "eyes", "on", "the", "prize", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "NNS", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 545, "question": "But is it as simple as that?", "question_tokens": ["But", "is", "it", "as", "simple", "as", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 546, "answer": "I definitely believe that builds a great foundation.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "definitely", "believe", "that", "builds", "a", "great", "foundation", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "WRB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "WP", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 556, "question": "What do you say to those people who just see a gang as the only place to find anyone that cares about them?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "say", "to", "those", "people", "who", "just", "see", "a", "gang", "as", "the", "only", "place", "to", "find", "anyone", "that", "cares", "about", "them", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NNS", "WP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 557, "answer": "Well, yeah, I would say to anyone who feels that through a gang is where they can find love -- you have to look at the results of people who join gangs.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "yeah", ",", "I", "would", "say", "to", "anyone", "who", "feels", "that", "through", "a", "gang", "is", "where", "they", "can", "find", "love", "--", "you", "have", "to", "look", "at", "the", "results", "of", "people", "who", "join", "gangs", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 566, "question": "If I told you could only do one thing the rest of your life, you could write poetry, you could write make or you could make films, which one would you take?", "question_tokens": ["If", "I", "told", "you", "could", "only", "do", "one", "thing", "the", "rest", "of", "your", "life", ",", "you", "could", "write", "poetry", ",", "you", "could", "write", "make", "or", "you", "could", "make", "films", ",", "which", "one", "would", "you", "take", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "CD", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VB", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NNS", ",", "WDT", "CD", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 567, "answer": "Making films.", "answer_tokens": ["Making", "films", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 576, "question": "But how do you deal with all that, all the attention you get?", "question_tokens": ["But", "how", "do", "you", "deal", "with", "all", "that", ",", "all", "the", "attention", "you", "get", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "DT", ",", "DT", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 577, "answer": "I try to put things in perspective.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "try", "to", "put", "things", "in", "perspective", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 580, "question": "I mean, without wishing to intrude at all, Common, you weren't responsible for Serena Williams' temper tantrum the other day on the court, right?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "without", "wishing", "to", "intrude", "at", "all", ",", "Common", ",", "you", "were", "n't", "responsible", "for", "Serena", "Williams", "'", "temper", "tantrum", "the", "other", "day", "on", "the", "court", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 581, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Serena Williams"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 600, "question": "Just don't play her at tennis, right?", "question_tokens": ["Just", "do", "n't", "play", "her", "at", "tennis", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP$", "IN", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 601, "answer": "I wouldn't have a chance.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "n't", "have", "a", "chance", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 618, "question": "Christina, how are you?", "question_tokens": ["Christina", ",", "how", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 619, "answer": "I'm well.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "well", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 622, "question": "Do you wake up every day looking in the mirror thinking, you're the sexiest woman alive?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "wake", "up", "every", "day", "looking", "in", "the", "mirror", "thinking", ",", "you", "'re", "the", "sexiest", "woman", "alive", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "RP", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBG", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 623, "answer": "No, sir.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "sir", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "``", "NNP", "''", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "RB", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 629, "question": "I think ugh, what do I have to do today?", "question_tokens": ["I", "think", "ugh", ",", "what", "do", "I", "have", "to", "do", "today", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 630, "answer": "ORGAN: I loved that \"Esquire\" interview, because it had so many lovely nuggets in it.", "answer_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "I", "loved", "that", "``", "Esquire", "''", "interview", ",", "because", "it", "had", "so", "many", "lovely", "nuggets", "in", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 645, "question": "Is he as ridiculously romantic as he seems?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "he", "as", "ridiculously", "romantic", "as", "he", "seems", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 646, "answer": "He is.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 652, "question": "How does he deal with the fact that there are million and millions, if not billions of men around the world now who are coveting his wife?", "question_tokens": ["How", "does", "he", "deal", "with", "the", "fact", "that", "there", "are", "million", "and", "millions", ",", "if", "not", "billions", "of", "men", "around", "the", "world", "now", "who", "are", "coveting", "his", "wife", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "EX", "VBP", "CD", "CC", "NNS", ",", "IN", "RB", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "WP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 653, "answer": "That's very sweet of you to say.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "very", "sweet", "of", "you", "to", "say", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 671, "question": "Does it annoy you?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "it", "annoy", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 672, "answer": "People have been very positive and complimentary, which is really nice.", "answer_tokens": ["People", "have", "been", "very", "positive", "and", "complimentary", ",", "which", "is", "really", "nice", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 679, "question": "There's a kind of slight dilemma there, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["There", "'s", "a", "kind", "of", "slight", "dilemma", "there", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "EX", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 680, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 690, "question": "Do you think we are in a much better place now?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "we", "are", "in", "a", "much", "better", "place", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 691, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 692, "question": "Or do you think that kind of overt, male dominated regime still exists?", "question_tokens": ["Or", "do", "you", "think", "that", "kind", "of", "overt", ",", "male", "dominated", "regime", "still", "exists", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "JJ", "VBN", "NN", "RB", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 693, "answer": "I think that we are in a much better place now.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "that", "we", "are", "in", "a", "much", "better", "place", "now", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 704, "question": "What?", "question_tokens": ["What", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "."], "aSentId": 705, "answer": "Jack.", "answer_tokens": ["Jack", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 708, "question": "Thinking of you?", "question_tokens": ["Thinking", "of", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 709, "answer": "I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Allison Pearson"]}, "docId": "110916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NNP", "NN", ":", "NN", "``", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 718, "question": "What is this all about?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "this", "all", "about", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "DT", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 719, "answer": "This movie is based on Allison Pearson's (ph) book \"I Don't Know How She Does It.\"", "answer_tokens": ["This", "movie", "is", "based", "on", "Allison", "Pearson", "'s", "(", "ph", ")", "book", "``", "I", "Do", "n't", "Know", "How", "She", "Does", "It", ".", "''"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", ":", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "TO", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "POS", "NN", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 722, "question": "What's your conclusion?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "your", "conclusion", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 723, "answer": "Um, I -- my conclusion after talking to so many women who have seen the film is that everyone's take is different.", "answer_tokens": ["Um", ",", "I", "--", "my", "conclusion", "after", "talking", "to", "so", "many", "women", "who", "have", "seen", "the", "film", "is", "that", "everyone", "'s", "take", "is", "different", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 729, "question": "You must be tempted to see a little patter of mini- Hendricks' feet, aren't you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "must", "be", "tempted", "to", "see", "a", "little", "patter", "of", "mini-", "Hendricks", "'", "feet", ",", "are", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "RB", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 730, "answer": "Not right now I'm not.", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "right", "now", "I", "'m", "not", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Hendricks"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "VBG", "NNS", ",", "DT", "NNS", ",", "TO", "VB", "JJS", ",", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 732, "question": "Does that concern you?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "that", "concern", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 733, "answer": "I really look at working mothers, all mothers, to be honest, in awe.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "really", "look", "at", "working", "mothers", ",", "all", "mothers", ",", "to", "be", "honest", ",", "in", "awe", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 745, "question": "If he saw you take the money, and he saw you get in the car, then why didn't he say anything?", "question_tokens": ["If", "he", "saw", "you", "take", "the", "money", ",", "and", "he", "saw", "you", "get", "in", "the", "car", ",", "then", "why", "did", "n't", "he", "say", "anything", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "WRB", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 746, "answer": "I have no idea.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "have", "no", "idea", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 761, "question": "How are you feeling about that, lucky?", "question_tokens": ["How", "are", "you", "feeling", "about", "that", ",", "lucky", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", ",", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 762, "answer": "I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 774, "question": "And thank Donald Draper for all his terrible behavior?", "question_tokens": ["And", "thank", "Donald", "Draper", "for", "all", "his", "terrible", "behavior", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 775, "answer": "I love your optimism right now.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "love", "your", "optimism", "right", "now", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Donald Draper"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 789, "question": "It has to be just straight, right?", "question_tokens": ["It", "has", "to", "be", "just", "straight", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "RB", "JJ", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 790, "answer": "That's right.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]